serverdeals.org 2018-10-09

# Server Deals Company Privacy Policy - ServerDeals.com

Looking for our [Terms of Service](https://www.serverdeals.com/terms-of-service/)?

This Privacy Policy describes the information we, Nexeon Technologies, Inc. (“ServerDeals”), collect from you, what we do with the information, and our information security practices. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us.

When you sign up for our service, we will ask you to provide contact information such as your name, address, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses, and payment information such as credit card number and expiration date. We may ask you to complete user surveys, and to provide certain demographic information, such as age, gender, special interests, etc.

You do not have to provide this type of information to use our service if you do not want to. If you contact us for customer support, we may also ask you for information about your operating system, software and other technical matters. When you visit our Web site we will capture your IP Address, time of and duration of visit, and time and duration of the pages on our Web site that you view. We may tie this information to the personally identifiable information we have about you. We will also place a cookie that will identify you to us as a repeat visitor or a customer when you visit our Web site. We may tie this cookie to the personally identifiable information we have about you. If we send you an e-mail, we may include a marker that will allow us to identify e-mail that is opened and viewed.

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary and required to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on ServerDeals. ServerDeals websites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that ServerDeals is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

The ServerDeals Privacy Policy as described herein applies solely to information collected by ServerDeals.

Use of Personally Identifiable Information

We will use your personally identifiable information only as follows:  
1: For payment purposes and to provide customer support;  
2: To announce special offers or provide other information from time to time via e-mail.We may also send e-mail announcing special offers by our third parties, but we will not provide the third parties with your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information. If you do not wish to receive these e-mails, you may opt out of future e-mails at any time by following the instructions included in the e-mail.  
3: To improve our service and the marketing of our service. For example, we may use the information we gather from user surveys, demographic data, and web site visits to help us improve or target our Web site and customize your visit.  
We will not provide any personally identifiable information about you to any other person other than:  
4: a person or company who acquires our business;  
5: third parties who perform services on our behalf (such as payment processing), subject to the third party agreeing with us that it will keep your personally identifiable information confidential;

We absolutely do not transfer or sell your information for inclusion on third party e-mail or other marketing lists.
